vladi-private-islands.de 2016-11-29

# Privacy Statement / Disclaimer - Vladi Private Islands

**1\. Applicability  **  
This privacy statement explains the nature, scope and purposes of the gathering and use of personal data by the responsible provider - Vladi Private Islands GmbH, Ballindamm 26, 20095 Hamburg, [info@vladi.de](mailto:info@vladi.de), 040/33 00 00 - on this website (hereafter referred to as "The Offer"). The legal basis of this Data Protection declaration is contained in the German Federal Data Protection Act (BDSG) and the German Telemedia Act (TMG).  
Die rechtlichen Grundlagen des Datenschutzes finden sich im Bundesdatenschutzgesetz (BDSG) und dem Telemediengesetz (TMG). 

**2\. Extent of Survey, Purpose and Deletion of Data  **  

**2.1 Access Data / Server Log Files  **  
The provider (or alternatively the webspace provider) collects data about every attempt to access The Offer (so-called Server Log Files). The access data includes: Name of file accessed, date and time of access, data volume transferred, report on successful access, the identity of information about the user's browser and operating system, the referrer URL (website from which access was initiated), the IP address and the name of the enquiring internet service provider. The log data will only be used by the provider for statistical evaluation for the purposes of operating, security and optimizing of the offer. The operator reserves the right to check the Log Files if - based on concrete evidence - there is justified evidence of illegal usage.  

**2.2 First Contact**    
After making contact with the provider (for example via the contact form or via e-mail) the user data will be saved electronically in order to further process your request and to assist with possible follow-up questions.  

**2.3 Newsletter**  
In the newsletter, we inform readers about us and our special offers. If you would like to receive the newsletter, we require a valid e-mail address from you as well as information which permits us to check that you are the holder of the e-mail address indicated or otherwise that the holder of the address indicated agrees to receive the newsletter. No other data will be collected. The data you provide us with will only be used for sending the newsletter and will not be disclosed to third parties. When you register for our newsletter, we store your IP-address and the date of registration. The storage of this information only serves as proof in such a case where a third party misuses an email address and registers for the receipt of the newsletter without the knowledge of the person entitled to receive the newsletter. Your consent for storing the data, the e-mail address as well as the use of the data and email address for sending the newsletter can be withdrawn at any time. You can withdraw your consent either via a link in the newsletter itself, through your profile area or by sending a message to the contact details listed above.  

**2.4 Integration of Services and Third Party Content**  
It may happen, that third party content, for example, YouTube videos, geographical information from Google-Maps, RSS-Feeds or graphics from other websites, may be integrated within the online offer. This presupposes that the providers of this content (hereinafter referred to as “Third Parties”) will use the user’s IP address. Without the IP address it would not be possible to send the content to the browsers of the respective users. The IP address is required in order to present the content. We strive only to use content from providers which only use the IP address to deliver content. However, we have no control over whether the “Third Parties” save the IP addresses for statistical purposes, for example. Insofar as this is known to us, we will clarify the users about it. 

  **2.5 Cookies**  
"Cookies" are small files which make it possible to store specific user-related details on the user's terminal device (PC, smartphone etc). They serve the purpose of making websites more user-friendly (for example, by saving the log-in details). They also serve to collect the statistical data about the website usage and then analyze the data in order to improve the offer. Users can influence the input of Cookies. Most browsers possess the option of either limiting storing Cookies or prevent them completely. However you will be informed that the usage and specially the user comfort is limited without Cookies.  
You can administrate many Online-Ad-Cookies of companies through the US homepage [http://www.aboutads.info/choices/](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/) or the EU homepage [www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/your-ad-choices/](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/your-ad-choices/).

**2.6 Registration Function**  
The data provided for registration purposes is used for the purpose of the use of the offer.  Users have the possibility to access information relevant to the offer or registration, such as changes in the range of offers or technical circumstances. The data collected can be seen from the input mask used for registration. This includes e-mail, password, title and name.  

**2.7 Google Analytics**  
This offer uses Google Analytics, a web analysis tool of Google Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses so-called “Cookies”, which are text files that are saved on the user’s computer and which enable an analysis of the usage of the website. Information generated through the Cookies about the usage of this website by the user is generally transferred to a Google server in the US and stored there. In case of an activation of the IP anonymisation on this website, Google will abbreviate the user’s IP address within the member nations of the European Union or other signatory states of the agreements on the European Economic Area. There are only a few exceptional cases, where the full IP address will be directed to a Google Server in the US and abbreviated there. The IP anonymisation is active on this website. On behalf of the website operator, Google will use this information, in order to evaluate the usage of the website by the user, compile reports on the website activities and provide further services in terms of website and internet usage to the website owner. The IP address submitted from your browser by Google Analytics, will not be merged with other Google data. Users can prevent the installation of Cookies by activating the relevant browser-software settings. However, users will be informed that in this case, it is very likely that not all features on this website can be used to their full extent. Furthermore, users can prevent the acquisition of information generated by Cookies on website based data (including IP address) being directed to as well as evaluated by Google by downloading and installing the following browser plug-in: [http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=de](http://www.vladi-private-islands.de/ccds/2.7%20Google%20Analytics%20This%20offer%20uses%20Google%20Analytics,%20a%20web%20analysis%20tool%20of%20Google%20Inc.%20\(%E2%80%9CGoogle%E2%80%9D\).%20Google%20Analytics%20uses%20so-called%20%E2%80%9CCookies%E2%80%9D,%20which%20are%20text%20files%20that%20are%20saved%20on%20the%20user%E2%80%99s%20computer%20and%20which%20enable%20an%20analysis%20of%20the%20usage%20of%20the%20website.%20Information%20generated%20through%20the%20Cookies%20about%20the%20usage%20of%20this%20website%20by%20the%20user%20is%20generally%20transferred%20to%20a%20Google%20server%20in%20the%20US%20and%20stored%20there.%20%20In%20case%20of%20an%20activation%20of%20the%20IP%20anonymisation%20on%20this%20website,%20Google%20will%20abbreviate%20the%20user%E2%80%99s%20IP%20address%20within%20the%20member%20nations%20of%20the%20European%20Union%20or%20other%20signatory%20states%20of%20the%20agreements%20on%20the%20European%20Economic%20Area.%20There%20are%20only%20a%20few%20exceptional%20cases,%20where%20the%20full%20IP%20address%20will%20be%20directed%20to%20a%20Google%20Server%20in%20the%20US%20and%20abbreviated%20there.%20The%20IP%20anonymisation%20is%20active%20on%20this%20website.%20On%20behalf%20of%20the%20website%20operator,%20Google%20will%20use%20this%20information,%20in%20order%20to%20evaluate%20the%20usage%20of%20the%20website%20by%20the%20user,%20compile%20reports%20on%20the%20website%20activities%20and%20provide%20further%20services%20in%20terms%20of%20website%20and%20internet%20usage%20to%20the%20website%20owner.%20The%20IP%20address%20submitted%20from%20your%20browser%20by%20Google%20Analytics,%20will%20not%20be%20merged%20with%20other%20Google%20data.%20Users%20can%20prevent%20the%20installation%20of%20Cookies%20by%20activating%20the%20relevant%20browser-software%20settings.%20However,%20users%20will%20be%20informed%20that%20in%20this%20case,%20it%20is%20very%20likely%20that%20not%20all%20features%20on%20this%20website%20can%20be%20used%20to%20their%20full%20extent.%20Furthermore,%20users%20can%20prevent%20the%20acquisition%20of%20information%20generated%20by%20Cookies%20on%20website%20based%20data%20\(including%20IP%20address\)%20being%20%20%20directed%20to%20as%20well%20as%20evaluated%20by%20Google%20by%20downloading%20and%20installing%20the%20following%20browser%20plug-in:%20http:/tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=de.).As an alternative to browser add-ons or within browsers on mobile devices, please click on this link, in order to prevent the collection of Google Analytics within this website in the future. In doing so, an opt-out cookie will be saved on your device. Should you delete your cookies, you must click on the link again.  

**2.8 Deletion of Data**  
A deletion of your personal data takes place provided that no legal retention obligation exists and you have made a claim that all data needs to be deleted as soon as it is no longer connected with the purpose of storage or also if the storage is prohibited due to other legal reasons.   

**3\. Responsible for Data Handling  **  
VLADI PRIVATE ISLANDS GmbH    
Ballindamm 26    
20095 Hamburg   
Germany    
Managing director: Farhad Vladi  

**4\. Handling of Personal Data**  
So far as personal data is being provided, we will only use this data to reply to inquiries, for the execution of closed contracts and for technical administration. Personal data will only be given to third parties, when these are required in order to close a contract or needed for accounting matters. This will happen only, if you have agreed to this beforehand. You have the right to withdraw your consent at any time.  

**5\. Usage of Personal Data for Commercial Purposes  **  
In general, it is not necessary to provide your personal data for the use of our website. However, in order for us to be able to fulfill our service, we may require this information.  This refers to the delivery of information material or ordered goods, as well as to answer individual requests.      
When you engage us with a service or order of goods, we will request and save your personal data, only for the purpose of the provision of this service or for the implementation of the contract. In case we do perform one of the following actions or provide any other services, we will ask you for your personal data and save this information. You will be requested on the relevant section of our website to agree to the following:       
\- Mailing of newsletters    
\- Mailing of offers and catalogues   
\- Further services and offers that will require consent for collecting data      
When you have registered with your email address for our newsletter, we will use your email address beyond the contract handling for our own advertising purposes until you cancel the newsletter.     
In case you wish to change your settings regarding these matters, please contact us by sending an email to [datenschutz@vladi.de  
](mailto:datenschutz@vladi.de)Your personal and anonymous data will primarily be used by the employees of VLADI PRIVATE ISLANDS for the purpose of the points stated above.  

**6\. Information, Changes Deletion and Updates**    
Upon request, the user has the right to receive information on stored personal data, which is free of charge. Furthermore the user has the right to correct data, which is invalid, block and delete personal data, as far as no legal retention obligation exists.
